The young mistress
العشيقة الشابة
and the young master.
والسيد الشاب.
Everyone, look!
الجميع، انظروا!
What rare guests.
ما هؤلاء الضيوف النادرين؟
Why are you even coming here now?
لماذا أتيت إلى هنا الآن؟
Our restaurant will be closing in a few days.
سيتم إغلاق مطعمنا خلال بضعة أيام.
Don't you realize
ألا تدرك؟
that this Fulu Restaurant
أن هذا مطعم فولو
has been barely staying afloat?
لقد كان بالكاد قادرا على البقاء طافيا؟
All because of
كل ذلك بسبب
a rich young master who stays home
سيد شاب غني يبقى في المنزل
going crazy all day long.
مجنون طوال اليوم.
Hoping for resurrection.
على أمل القيامة.
Keep dreaming.
استمر بالحلم.
The old master used to
كان المعلم القديم يستخدم
want to keep it as a memento.
أريد الاحتفاظ بها كتذكار.
Now
الآن
the second young master is in charge,
السيد الشاب الثاني هو المسؤول،
so of course it's closed.
لذا بالطبع فهو مغلق.
Don't mind that.
لا يهمك ذلك.
Everyone,
الجميع،
Fulu Restaurant is the foundation of the Liu family's fortune.
يعد مطعم فولو الأساس لثروة عائلة ليو.
I promise you all
أعدكم جميعا
that no matter what,
أنه مهما كان الأمر،
we will never close down.
لن نغلق أبدًا.
Starting today,
ابتداء من اليوم،
the restaurant will be reorganized.
سيتم إعادة تنظيم المطعم.
The eldest young master and I promise you
السيد الشاب الأكبر وأنا أعدك
that within three months,
أنه في غضون ثلاثة أشهر،
we will definitely restore the restaurant to its former glory.
سوف نقوم بالتأكيد باستعادة المطعم إلى مجده السابق.
It will become
سوف تصبح
the most popular restaurant in Yun City.
المطعم الأكثر شعبية في مدينة يون.
Fulu Restaurant won't abandon anyone.
مطعم فولو لن يتخلى عن أحد.
I hope everyone can cheer up
أتمنى أن يتمكن الجميع من التشجيع
and work hard with us.
والعمل الجاد معنا.
Madam,
سيدتي،
I wronged you before.
لقد ظلمتك من قبل.
Thank you for letting bygones be bygones.
شكرا لك على ترك الماضي يصبح ماضيا.
Young Master and Madam,
السيد الشاب والسيدة،
I will definitely be dedicated from now on
بالتأكيد سأكون مخصصًا من الآن فصاعدًا
and help you both run Fulu Restaurant well.
ومساعدتكما في إدارة مطعم فولو بشكل جيد.
I'll follow the Young Master too.
سأتبع السيد الشاب أيضًا.
We will all follow the Young Master and Madam
سوف نتبع جميعًا السيد الشاب والسيدة
with complete dedication.
بكل تفانٍ.
I've gathered all the elders today
لقد جمعت كل الشيوخ اليوم
because we have important matters to discuss.
لأن لدينا أمورًا مهمة لمناقشتها.
Recently,
حديثاً،
our Liu family business has been doing quite well.
لقد كانت أعمال عائلة ليو ناجحة جدًا.
This is all thanks to
كل هذا بفضل
the Second Young Master's excellent management.
الإدارة الممتازة للشاب الثاني.
In just over a month,
في أكثر من شهر بقليل،
he has doubled the Liu family's revenue.
لقد ضاعف إيرادات عائلة ليو.
The master's decision to choose the Second Young Master as his successor
قرار المعلم باختيار المعلم الشاب الثاني خلفًا له
truly shows his keen eye for talent.
يظهر حقًا اهتمامه الشديد بالموهبة.
Yes, indeed.
نعم بالفعل.
Now,
الآن،
only the Fulu Restaurant
فقط مطعم فولو
still shows no improvement
لا يزال لا يظهر أي تحسن
and continues to operate at a loss.
وتستمر في العمل بخسارة.
Without the support from other Liu family businesses,
بدون الدعم من الشركات العائلية الأخرى لعائلة ليو،
Fulu Restaurant would have closed down long ago.
لقد تم إغلاق مطعم فولو منذ زمن طويل.
Although the Liu family can sustain it for now,
على الرغم من أن عائلة ليو قادرة على تحمل ذلك في الوقت الحالي،
this cannot continue indefinitely.
لا يمكن أن يستمر هذا إلى أجل غير مسمى.
So I've gathered all the elders today
لقد جمعت كل الشيوخ اليوم
to discuss
لمناقشة
what should be done with Fulu Restaurant.
ماذا يجب أن نفعل مع مطعم فولو؟
Previously,
سابقًا،
when the master was still with us,
عندما كان المعلم لا يزال معنا،
the restaurant was his cherished project.
وكان المطعم مشروعه العزيز.
Now that he's gone,
الآن بعد أن رحل،
and the restaurant continues to lose money year after year.
ويستمر المطعم في خسارة الأموال عامًا بعد عام.
Well,
حسنًا،
there's really no need to keep it running anymore.
لم تعد هناك حاجة حقيقية لإبقائه قيد التشغيل بعد الآن.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
If everyone here agrees today,
إذا اتفق الجميع هنا اليوم،
we will officially decide
سوف نقرر رسميا
to close the restaurant.
لإغلاق المطعم.
Fulu Restaurant cannot be closed!
لا يمكن إغلاق مطعم فولو!
Young Master!
سيدي الشاب!
Brother!
أخ!
This Fulu Restaurant
مطعم فولو هذا
is the foundation of our Liu family's prosperity.
هو أساس ازدهار عائلة ليو.
It absolutely cannot be closed.
لا يمكن إغلاقه على الإطلاق.
Brother,
أخ،
you make it sound so easy.
أنت تجعل الأمر يبدو سهلاً للغاية.
If we don't close the restaurant,
إذا لم نغلق المطعم،
then we'll have to keep supporting it with our other businesses.
ثم يتعين علينا الاستمرار في دعمها من خلال أعمالنا الأخرى.
Why don't you ask
لماذا لا تسأل؟
if the others are willing to do that?
إذا كان الآخرون على استعداد للقيام بذلك؟
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
we understand that
نحن نفهم ذلك
Fulu Restaurant was started by the master and mistress.
تم افتتاح مطعم فولو على يد السيد والسيدة.
We understand your reluctance to let it go.
نحن نفهم ترددك في التخلي عنه.
However,
لكن،
sentiment...
مشاعر...
cannot overcome reality.
لا يمكن التغلب على الواقع.
Yes, Young Master.
نعم سيدي الشاب.
Ever since the famous dishes that Fulu Restaurant relied on were lost,
منذ أن فقدت الأطباق الشهيرة التي كان يعتمد عليها مطعم فولو،
customer interest has been declining.
لقد انخفض اهتمام العملاء.
This day was bound to come.
لقد كان من المتوقع أن يأتي هذا اليوم.
You must face reality.
يجب عليك مواجهة الواقع.
Respected elders,
أيها الشيوخ المحترمين،
we have just recreated
لقد قمنا بإعادة إنشائها للتو
the classic signature dishes of Fulu Restaurant.
الأطباق الكلاسيكية المميزة لمطعم فولو.
Since you're all here,
بما أنكم جميعا هنا،
please taste them first
من فضلك تذوقهم أولا
before making any decision.
قبل اتخاذ أي قرار.
This...
هذا...
I believe with these dishes,
أعتقد مع هذه الأطباق،
our Fulu Restaurant
مطعمنا فولو
will certainly become the number one restaurant in Yun City.
سيصبح بالتأكيد المطعم رقم واحد في مدينة يون.
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
you're being far too ambitious.
أنت طموح للغاية.
You should know that
يجب أن تعلم أن
since Master Jiang Huai's incident,
منذ حادثة السيد جيانغ هواي،
our restaurant
مطعمنا
has never recreated the original flavors.
لم يتم إعادة إنتاج النكهات الأصلية أبدًا.
Uncle Wang,
العم وانغ
rest assured,
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك،
the taste of these dishes
طعم هذه الأطباق
is guaranteed to be
من المؤكد أن يكون
exactly the same as before.
بالضبط كما كان من قبل.
Brother,
أخ،
you knowing how to cook
أنت تعرف كيف تطبخ
is absolutely preposterous!
إنه أمر سخيف تمامًا!
Brother, is your madness acting up again?
أخي هل جنونك يعود مرة أخرى؟
Serve the dishes!
قدم الأطباق!
Let all the elders taste
فليتذوقه كل الشيوخ
the signature dishes of my Fulu Restaurant.
الأطباق المميزة لمطعم فولو.
Qian Yiyu
تشيان يو
Steamed crab meat lion's head meatballs,
لحم السلطعون المطهو ​​على البخار، كرات لحم رأس الأسد،
crystal pork terrine,
تيرين لحم الخنزير الكريستالي،
white-coated shrimp,
الروبيان ذو الفراء الأبيض،
Wensi tofu,
التوفو وينسي,
dried scallops with cattail.
المحار المجفف مع نبات القصب.
These were all signature dishes of the Fulu Restaurant back in the day.
كانت هذه كلها أطباق مميزة لمطعم فولو في الماضي.
Please enjoy.
من فضلك استمتع.
This truly tastes like the restaurant's original flavors.
هذا الطعم يشبه حقًا النكهات الأصلية للمطعم.
Oh my, this dish!
أوه، هذا الطبق!
I haven't tasted food like this for many years.
لم أتذوق طعامًا مثل هذا منذ سنوات عديدة.
Young master,
سيدي الشاب،
how did you manage this?
كيف تمكنت من ذلك؟
Please help me.
من فضلك ساعدني.
Are you really
هل انت حقا
going to help the young master run the restaurant?
هل ستساعد السيد الشاب في إدارة المطعم؟
Aren't you in love with the second young master?
هل أنت في حب الشاب الثاني؟
Now that he's in charge.
الآن أصبح مسؤولا.
You two...
انتما الاثنان...
Silin isn't as irresponsible as you think.
سيلين ليس غير مسؤول كما تعتقد.
Fulu Restaurant is the last memento from his late mother.
مطعم فولو هو التذكار الأخير من والدته الراحلة.
Since I married him,
منذ أن تزوجته،
I want to help him fulfill his wish.
أريد أن أساعده في تحقيق أمنيته.
Fine.
بخير.
This is
هذا هو
from your biological father,
من والدك البيولوجي،
Jiang Huai.
جيانغ هواي.
Take it.
خذها.
Where did you get this from?
من أين حصلت على هذا؟
Years ago,
منذ سنوات،
when your parents had the accident,
عندما تعرض والداك للحادث،
I couldn't arrive in time to save them.
لم أستطع الوصول في الوقت المناسب لإنقاذهم.
It's the biggest regret of my life.
إنه أكبر ندم في حياتي.
When I finally arrived,
عندما وصلت أخيرا،
it was already too late.
لقد كان الوقت متأخرا بالفعل.
I only found
لقد وجدت فقط
this cookbook on your father's body.
هذا كتاب الطبخ على جسد والدك.
Now,
الآن،
it's finally returned to its rightful owner.
لقد عاد أخيرًا إلى مالكه الشرعي.
But I
ولكن انا
have nothing left now.
لم يبق لي شيء الآن.
No.
لا.
You have me.
أنت تملكني.
And you have Fulu Restaurant.
ولديك مطعم فولو.
Restaurant.
مطعم.
This...
هذا...
How is this possible?
كيف هذا ممكن؟
With this recipe,
مع هذه الوصفة،
our restaurant
مطعمنا
can make a comeback.
يمكن أن يعود مرة أخرى.
Yes, indeed.
نعم بالفعل.
Since all the elders have already tasted it,
وبما أن جميع الشيوخ قد ذاقوا ذلك بالفعل،
you should now believe that
يجب أن تصدق الآن أن
the young master's promise to revive Fulu Restaurant
وعد السيد الشاب بإحياء مطعم فولو
wasn't just empty talk, right?
لم يكن مجرد حديث فارغ، أليس كذلك؟
But...
لكن...
These are all extremely difficult dishes to prepare.
تعتبر هذه الأطباق كلها صعبة للغاية في التحضير.
The knife skills are so precise,
مهارات السكين دقيقة للغاية،
the cooking temperature so exact.
درجة حرارة الطبخ دقيقة جدًا.
Even with the original recipes,
حتى مع الوصفات الأصلية،
without decades of culinary experience,
بدون عقود من الخبرة في الطهي،
he couldn't possibly make them!
من غير الممكن أن يتمكن من صنعهم!
Young master, young mistress,
السيد الشاب، السيدة الشابة،
how did you actually make these dishes?
كيف قمت بتحضير هذه الأطباق فعليا؟
Of course we couldn't make these dishes ourselves.
بالطبع لم نتمكن من صنع هذه الأطباق بأنفسنا.
Oh? Then how...
أوه؟ إذن كيف...
Come up.
هيا تعال.
Aren't these all the old
أليست هذه كلها قديمة؟
masters who started the business with the master?
السادة الذين بدأوا العمل مع السيد؟
Yes.
نعم.
Weren't they all trained by Master Zhang Wen?
ألم يتم تدريبهم جميعًا على يد المعلم تشانغ وين؟
These old masters
هؤلاء الأساتذة القدامى
were all hired when my parents opened the Fulu Restaurant.
لقد تم تعيينهم جميعًا عندما افتتح والداي مطعم فولو.
But later the business declined dramatically,
ولكن في وقت لاحق تراجعت الأعمال بشكل كبير،
and they all left to make a living elsewhere.
وغادروا جميعا للبحث عن لقمة العيش في مكان آخر.
But I've kept in touch with them all these years.
لكنني بقيت على اتصال معهم كل هذه السنوات.
When they heard I was reviving Fulu Restaurant,
عندما سمعوا أنني أقوم بإحياء مطعم فولو،
they immediately came back to help me.
لقد عادوا على الفور لمساعدتي.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
The master and mistress have shown us tremendous kindness.
لقد أظهر لنا السيد والسيدة لطفًا كبيرًا.
We will definitely help you restore the Fulu Restaurant.
سنقوم بالتأكيد بمساعدتك في استعادة مطعم Fulu.
These years, with all the family troubles,
في هذه السنوات، مع كل المشاكل العائلية،
it's thanks to the Young Master's support.
وهذا بفضل دعم السيد الشاب.
For this reason alone,
ولهذا السبب وحده،
I must do my part.
يجب علي أن أقوم بدوري.
So, Liu Silin.
لذلك، ليو سيلين.
All these years you've been pretending to be crazy,
طوال هذه السنوات كنت تتظاهر بالجنون،
secretly maintaining relationships with these old staff,
الحفاظ على العلاقات سراً مع هؤلاء الموظفين القدامى،
just to set me up today.
فقط لإعدادي اليوم.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
can the Fulu Restaurant
هل يمكن لمطعم فولو
reopen for business now?
إعادة فتح الأعمال الآن؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
I never thought that we old folks
لم أكن أعتقد أبدًا أننا كبار السن
would one day...
سوف يحدث يوما ما...
To see our restaurant
لرؤية مطعمنا
become the best in Yun City.
أصبح الأفضل في مدينة يون.
I, Silin, thank all the elders for your support.
أنا، سيلين، أشكر جميع الشيوخ على دعمكم.
Let go of me.
أتركني.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Yiyu, what do you mean?
يييو، ماذا تقصد؟
It's fine if you don't help me,
لا بأس إذا لم تساعدني،
but you're deliberately embarrassing me, aren't you?
لكنك تحرجني عمدًا، أليس كذلك؟
Silin is your elder brother.
سيلين هو أخوك الأكبر.
Why are you being so heartless,
لماذا أنت قاسي القلب هكذا؟
driving him to the wall?
دفعه إلى الحائط؟
Fulu Restaurant is the last memento the master left him.
مطعم فولو هو التذكار الأخير الذي تركه له المعلم.
Won't you even spare him this?
هل يمكنك أن توفر له هذا حتى؟
Don't mention my father to me.
لا تذكر لي والدي.
If my father hadn't favored him so much,
لو لم يكن والدي يفضله كثيرًا،
I wouldn't have faced so much contempt in this family.
لم أكن لأواجه كل هذا الاحتقار في هذه العائلة.
Liu Silin is just the favorite.
ليو سيلين هو المفضل فقط.
He was insane for so many years,
لقد كان مجنونًا لسنوات عديدة،
yet my father still left him a restaurant.
ومع ذلك فقد ترك لي والدي مطعمًا.
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
What did the master give me?
ماذا أعطاني المعلم؟
The master gave you the entire Liu family.
لقد أعطاك السيد عائلة ليو بأكملها.
Isn't that enough?
أليس هذا كافيا؟
What more do you have to complain about?
ماذا لديك أكثر لتشتكي منه؟
That wasn't given to me.
هذا لم يعط لي.
All of this...
كل هذا...
I earned it all through my own abilities.
لقد حصلت على كل ذلك بفضل قدراتي الخاصة.
Liu Silin was insane for so long.
لقد كان ليو سيلين مجنونًا لفترة طويلة.
The Liu family was maintained solely by me.
كانت عائلة ليو تعتمد علي وحدي.
The master had no choice.
لم يكن أمام السيد أي خيار.
I endured humiliation
لقد تحملت الإذلال
and bided my time.
وانتظرت الوقت المناسب.
I've waited so long.
لقد انتظرت لفترة طويلة.
I've been waiting for this day.
لقد كنت أنتظر هذا اليوم.
Yu.
يو.
[Credits]
[الاعتمادات]